Guide to the Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive 1961-2009 (bulk 1976-2005) MSS.171
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Artists Files
  - Brzezinski, Emilie Benes, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Buchanan, Beverly, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Buchanan, Beverly - Slides, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Buchen, Bill & Mary, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Buchen, Bill & Mary - Slides, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bul, Lee, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bunkley, Brit, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bunkley, Brit - Slides, 1984-1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Burden, Chris, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Burden, Chris, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Buren, Daniel, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Buren, Daniel [1 of 2], undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Buren, Daniel [2 of 2], undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Burko, Diane - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Burko, Diane - Reviews, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Burnley, Gary, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Burnley, Gary, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Burton, Scott, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Burton, Scott, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Bury, Paul, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Busch, Nancy, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Butler, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Butterfield, Deborah, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Butterfield, Deborah, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Byars, James Lee, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Byron, Kim, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - C (general), undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Cabrera, Patricio, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Cai, Guo-Qiang, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Calame, Ingrid, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Calder, Alexander, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Calder, Alexander, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Caldwell, Luisa, undated (Box 6, Folder 30A)
  - Campbell, David, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 30B)
  - Carasik, Karen, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Caravacho, Josley, undated (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_23cd235dbae396dd037de2678474060d)
  - Cardiff, Janet, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Carlson, Cynthia, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Carlson, Cynthia, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Caro, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Caro, Anothony, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Carpenter, James, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Carpenter, James [1 of 2], undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Carpenter, James [2 of 2], undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Carrera, Jackie, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Casabere, James, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Casabere, James, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Catlett, Elizabeth, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Cecere, Jennifer - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Cecere, Jennifer - Photos/Slides, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Celmins, Vija, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Cemin, Saint-Clair, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Cemin, Saint-Clair [1 of 4], undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Cemin, Saint-Clair [2 of 4], undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Cemin, Saint-Clair - "Irish Hunger Memorial Presenation" [3 of 4], undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Cemin, Saint-Clair [4 of 4], undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Cesar, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Chadwick, Lynn, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Chamberlain, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Chamberlain, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Chand, Nek, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Chand, Nek, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Chao, Bruce, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Chase, Colin (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cheng, Amy, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chia, Sandro, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chia, Sandro, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Chiarini, Dorina, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chihuly, Dale, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Chihuly, Dale [1 of 4], undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Chihuly, Dale [2 of 4], undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chihuly, Dale - Chihuly Visuals [3 of 4], undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Chihuly, Dale - Chihuly Visuals [4 of 4], undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chihuly, La Salle, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chillida, Eduardo, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Chillida, Eduardo, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Chin, Mel, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Chin, Mel, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Chorpenning, Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Chorpenning, Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Christo, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Christo & Jeanne Claude [1 of 5], undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Christo & Jeanne-Claude [2 of 5], undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Christo & Jeanne-Claude [3 of 5], undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Christo & Jeanne-Claude (CD) [4 of 5], undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Christo & Jeanne-Claude - "The Gates" [5 of 5], undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Chryssa, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Chryssa, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Chu, Anne, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Chun, Kwang-Young, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Chunn, Nancy, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Clark, James, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Clerk, Pierre, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Clodagh Design, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cochran, Malcolm, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Cockroff, Eva, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Cohen, Nancy, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Cole, Willie, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Colette, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Colette, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Colette, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Colette, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Connor, Maureen, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Conwill, Houston, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Coogan, Jay, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Coogan, Jay, undated (Box 7, Folder 43A)
  - Cooper, Ruffin, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 43B)
  - Cousagra, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Coyne, Petah, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Coyne, Petah, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Cragg, Tony, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cragg, Tony, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Craig-Martin, Michael, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Crawford, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Crawford, Thom Cooney - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Crespo, George, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Crile, Susan, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cucchi, Enzo, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Cucchi, Enzo, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cumming, Robert, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Currie, Steve, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Curtis, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Cutler-Shaw, Joyce, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Damast, Elba, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Damast, Elba, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Damast, Elba [2 of 2], undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - D'Arrigo, Elisa, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - D'Arrigo, Elisa, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Davidow, Julie, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Davidow, Julie - CD, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Davidson, Jean - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Davis, Brad, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Davis, Lisa Corinne, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Davis, Ron, undated (Box 8, Folder 24A)
  - Day, E.V., 2006 (Box 8, Folder 24B)
  - de Amaral, Olga, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - DeBellevue, Lucky, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - DeForest, Roy, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - de la Cova, Eric, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - DeMaria, Walter, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - de Monchaux, Cathy, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - DeMonte, Claudia, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - DeMonte, Claudia, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - De Movellan, Pedro Sanchez - Photos/Slides, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - De Movellan, Pedro Sanchez - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - de Saint Phalle, Niki, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - de Saint Phalle, Niki, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - De Staebler, Stephen, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Deacon, Richard, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Deacon, Richard, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Dean, Mark, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Dean, Tacita, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - de la Vega, James, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Delvoye, Wim, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Denes, Agnes [1 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Denes, Agnes (Irish Hunger Memorial Presentation) [2 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Denes, Agnes (Teardrop Pyramid) [3 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Denes, Agnes - Tree Mountain [4 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Denes, Agnes [5 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Denes, Agnes [6 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Denes Visuals, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Denes Proposals/Visuals [1 of 2], undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Denes Proposal Xeroxes [2 of 2], undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Denes Bio-Writing [1 of 3], undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Denes - "Wheatfield" [2 of 3], undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Denes Articles [3 of 3], undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Denes, Agnes, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Denes, Agnes [1 of 2], undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Denes, Agnes [2 of 2], undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Denes, Agnes, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Dennis, Donna, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Dennis, Donna, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Derdyk, Edith, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Di Benedetto, Steve, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Di Suvero, Mark, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Di Suvero, Mark, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Diaz de Santillana, Alessandro, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Dill, Lesley, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Dion, Mark, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dokoupil, Jiri Georg, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Dona, Lydia, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dona, Lydia, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Doner, Michele Oka - Reviews, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Doner, Michele Oka - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Donovan, Abigail, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Donovan, Tara, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Dougherty, Patrick, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Dougherty, Patrick, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Dowell, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Dowell, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Dowell, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Downer, Spelman Evans and other artists - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Downer, Spelman Evans - Proposals, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Downer, Spelman Evans - Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Doyle, Tom - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Doyle, Tom - Photos/Slides, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Driscoll, Ellen, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Driscoll, Ellen, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Dubuffet, Jean, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Dubuffet, Jean, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Duckworth, Ruth, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Duff, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Durant, Sam, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Dusenberry, Walter, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Dwyer, Nancy, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Dwyer, Nancy, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Eatherton, Tom - Photos/Slides, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Eatherton, Tom - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Echelman, Janet - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Edelstein, Barbara - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Edmier, Keith - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Edmier, Keith, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Edmier, Keith - Photos/Slides, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Edmier, Keith - Reviews, 1995-2002 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Edwards, Benjamin - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Edwards, Benjamin - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Edwards, Benjamin - Reviews, undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Edwards, Melvin - Reviews, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Einstein, Ula - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Einstein, Ula - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Eliasson, Olafur, undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Eliasson, Olafur - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Eliasson, Olafur - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Eliasson, Olafur - Reviews, undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Ellis, Stephen, undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Emin, Tracey - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1999-2005 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Emin, Tracey - Reviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Ericson, Kate and Ziegler, Mel, undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Ericson, Kate and Ziegler, Mel, undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Episalla, Joy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2004 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Escobar, Carolina, undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Escobar, Carolina, undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Etkins, Susan - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Essenhigh, Inka - Reviews, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Essenhigh, Inka - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2004 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Evenson, Bjorn, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Ewing, Lauren [1 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Ewing, Lauren [2 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Ewing, Lauren [3 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Ewing, Lauren - Penrose Plaza, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Ewing, Lauren - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Ewing, Lauren - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Ewing, Lauren, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fabiao, Solange - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fabre, Jan, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Fabro, Luciano - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Fahlen, C. - Photos/Slides, 1976-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Fajens, Michael, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Fasnacht, Heidi, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Feher, Tony - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2002-2005 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Fenley, Karen - Photos/Slides, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Fernandez, Terasita - Reviews, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Fernandez, Terasita - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Fernandez, Terasita - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1999 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Ferrer, Rafael - Photos/Slides, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Ferrer, Rafael - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Ferrara, Jackie [1 of 5], undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Ferrara, Jackie [3 of 5], undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Ferrara, Jackie [4 of 5], undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Ferrara, Jackie - Articles [1 of 5], undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Ferrara - Photo [1 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Ferrara - Reviews [2 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Ferrara, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Ferrara, Jackie [1 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Ferrara, Jackie [2 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Fine, Jud & Barbara McCarren - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Fine, Jud & Barbara McCarren - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Fine, Jud & Barbara McCarren - Reviews, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Finn, David - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Fischer, R. M. [1 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Fischer, R. M. Visuals [2 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Fischer, R. M. - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Fisher - Avalon Bay, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Fisher 17-54, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Fisher, Joel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Fisher, Joel - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Fisher, Joel - Reviews, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Fisher, Joel - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Joel Fisher, Loan Contract [1 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Joel Fisher, Loan Forms [2 of 2], undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Fisher, Naomi - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Fisher, Naomi - Reviews, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Fisher, Naomi - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2002 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Fisher, Vernon - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Fisher, Vernon - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998-2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Fisher, Vernon - Reviews, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Fishl, Eric - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Fitzgerald, Astrid - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Fitzgerald, Astrid - Reviews, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Fitzgerald, Astrid - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Fitzgibbons, Bill, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Flack, Audrey - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Flack, Audrey - Reviews, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Flack, Audrey - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Flanagan, Barry - Invitiations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Flanagan, Barry - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Flanagan, Barry - Photos/Slides, 1985, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Flavin, Dan - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Flavin, Dan - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1985, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Flavin, Dan - "Photos/Visuals", 1980, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Fleishner, Richard - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Fleishner, Richard - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Fleishner, Richard - Photos/Slides, 1971-1997 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Fleishner, Richard - Reviews, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Fleishner, Richard - Proposals, 1983-? (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Fleming, Linda - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Fleming, Linda - Photos/Slides, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Fleming, Linda - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Fleury, Sylvie - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Flukinger/ Harrah - Photos/Slides, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Fortuyn/O'Brien - Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Fosnacht, Heidi, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Fradkin, Lucy - Reviews, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Francis, Sam, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Freed, Hermine - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Freed, Hermine, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Freeman, Chris, undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Friedberg, Richard - Photos/Slides, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Friedberg, Richard - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1993 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Friedberg, Richard - Photos/Slides, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Friedman, Dara - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2004 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Friedman, Dara - Photos/Slides, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Friedman, Tom - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Friedmann, Gloria - Photos/Slides, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Fry, Leslie - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Fry, Leslie - Reviews, 1998-2003 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Furugo, Shuishi - Photos/Slides, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - G.R. Artists [1 of 2], 1995 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - G.R. Artists [2 of 2], 1995 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Galan, Julio - Photos/Slides, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Galgiani, Philip - Photos/Slides, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Galston, Beth - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Galston, Beth - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Garcia-Roig, Lillian - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Garcia-Roig, Lillian - Photos/Slides, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Garet, Jedd - Photos/Slides, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Gelfman, Lynne Golob - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Gelfman, Lynne Golob - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Gelfman, Lynne Golob - Reviews, 1997-2005 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Gerard, Michel, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Gerard, Michel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Gerard, Michel - Reviews, 1989 - 2003 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Gerard, Michel - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Giankos, Christos - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Giersbach, Cadence - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Giersbach, Cadence - Reviews, 1995-1998 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Giersbach, Cadence - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Giler, Mike - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 1987-2001 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Giler, Mike - Reviews, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Giler, Mike - Photos/Slides, 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Gilhooly, David - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Gilliam, Sam - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Gilliam, Sam, 1979-1984, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Gillick, Liam - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Gillick, Liam - Reviews, 1991-1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Gillman, Steve - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ginnerver, Charles - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Ginsberg, Elizabeth - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Ginsberg, Elizabeth - Photos/Slides, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Ginsberg, Elizabeth - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Ginzel, Andrews and Kristin Jones, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Gipe, Lawrence - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Gipe, Lawrence - Photos/Slides, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Gitman, Victoria - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Gitman, Victoria - Photos and Slides, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Gitman, Victoria - Reviews, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Giusti, Karin, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Giusti, Karin F. - Reviews, 1993, 1997-1998, 2000, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Giusti, Karin F. - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Glen, Robert, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Glen, Robert - Photos/Slides, undates (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Glesta, Anita - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2004 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Godfrey, DeWitt - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Godfrey, DeWitt - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Godfrey, DeWitt - Reviews, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Goldberg, Brad - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Goldman, Charles - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Goldman, Charles - Reviews, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Goldsworthy, Andy - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Goldsworthy, Andy - Reviews, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Goldsworthy, Andy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., 2005 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Goldsworthy, Andy - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Golub, Leon, 1988, 2000, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Gonzalez, Torres, Felix, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Gonzalez, Maria Elena, 2002, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Goodell, Kathy, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Gordillo, Gun - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Gordon, Russell, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Gormley, Antony, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Graham, Dan [1 of 2], 1996 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Graham, Dan [2 of 2], 1984-1990 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Graham, Dan - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Graham, Gloria - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Graham, Robert, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Graham, Rodney, 1997, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Granet, Ilona, undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Granet, Ilona - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Graupe-Pillard - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Graves, Bradford, undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Graves, Bradford - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Graves, Nancy - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Greene, Robert - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Greenblat, Rodney Alan, undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Greenblat, Rodney Alan - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 52)